Guide to the American Planning Association records, 1925-2015.
American Planning Association records,
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
American Planning Association records, 1925-2015
4075
American Planning Association
153.3 cubic ft.
Correspondence, reports, news releases, speeches, statements, biographies, mailing lists, photographs, programs, printed materials, applications, publicity materials, articles, an interview, newsletters, applications, minutes, conference records, audiotapes, films, microfilms, and files.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Contains office files and printed materials relating to planning conferences and programs; National Planning Awards submissions; and materials regarding planning education. Also includes minutes, newsletters, conference records, planning publications from various institutional entities now part of APA, proceedings from meetings, and audiotapes of lectures.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
In 1978, the American Society of Planning Officials (ASPO) merged with the American Institute of Planners (AIP) to form the American Planning Association (APA).
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Office files and printed materials relating to planning conferences and programs; National Planning Awards submissions; and materials regarding planning education. Correspondence, reports, news releases, speeches, statements, biographies, mailing lists, photographs, programs, printed materials, applications, and files pertaining to conferences and programs of the American Planning Association; included are files of Stephen L. Cochran (1980-84) and Israel Stollman; news releases, speeches, articles, an interview, and newsletters concerning the Urban Enterprise Zone Conference of APA's Washington, DC, Chapter (1981); reports, mailing lists, and publicity materials regarding the Dallas National Planning Conference (1982); applications from universities with planning programs for recognition by the APA National Education Development Committee (1979-84); and National Planning Awards submissions (1985 and 1987). Also, films and microfilms, and Dennis O'Harrow speeches and material.
Includes minutes, newsletters, conference records, numerous planning publications from various institutional entities now part of APA, proceedings from meetings, audiotapes of lectures, and other records and publications.
SUBJECTS
Names:
American Planning Association.; Cochran, Stephen L.; Stollman, Israel.; O'Harrow, Dennis, 1908-; American Planning Association. National Education Development Committee.; American Planning Association. Policy and Government Relations Conference (1981); American Planning Association. Urban Enterprise Zone Conference (1981: Washington, D.C.); Dallas National Planning Conference (1982)
Subjects:
City planning.; Regional planning.; Zoning.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
RELATED MATERIAL
See also: Guide to the American Society of Planning Officials Records ( collection #3247) and the Guide to the American Institute of Planners Records ( collection #4007).
CONTAINER LIST
- Israel Stollman correspondence, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 1-3)
- Chronological file, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 4-6)
- Israel Stollman chronological file, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Chronological file (outgoing), 1982 (Box 1, Folder 8-11)
- Raw data - student/ faculty ratio, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Annual reports (colleges and universities), 1982 (Box 1, Folder 13-17)
- Annual reports (colleges and universities), 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 18-19)
- Dual degrees - annual reports, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Statistics summary - recognition degree programs, 1980-1982 (Box 1, Folder 21-22)
- Miscellaneous information on planning degree programs, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Supplements to annual reports, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Downtown Park Competition, final report - Bellevue, Washington, 1984-1985 (Box 154)
- Washington, D.C. Chapter - Urban Enterprise Zone Conference
  - Washington, D.C. Chapter - Urban Enterprise Zone Conference-speakers, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Washington, D.C. Chapter - Urban Enterprise Zone Conference - logistic, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Washington, D.C. Chapter - Urban Enterprise Zone Conference - legislation, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Washington, D.C. Chapter - Urban Enterprise Zone Conference - news release, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Washington, D.C. Chapter - Urban Enterprise Zone Conference -publicity/ follow-up tape: interview Gail Garfield Schwartz, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Washington, D.C. Chapter - Urban Enterprise Zone Conference -program/newsletter, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Washington, D.C. Chapter - Urban Enterprise Zone Conference - speeches, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 31-32)
  - Washington, D.C. Chapter - Urban Enterprise Zone Conference - release, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Washington, D.C. Chapter - Urban Enterprise Zone Conference -background/articles, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 34-35)
- Rough transcripts, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 36-37)
- Policy and Government Relations Conference
  - Policy and Government Relations Conference - publicity summary, post mortem tape: Gail Garfield Schwartz interview at A. P. radio, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Policy and Government Relations Conference - publicity summary, post mortem, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Policy and Government Relations Conference - pre- and post-media releases, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Policy and Government Relations Conference - policy statements and revisions, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Policy and Government Relations Conference - policy statements and revisions, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Policy and Government Relations Conference - photo section -photographers: James Cosgrove, Deborah Rhoad, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Policy and Government Relations Conference - speeches/ speakers' biographies, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Speeches - February Policy Conference, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 4-5)
  - Policy and Government Relations Conference Program - correspondence background, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- APA National Conference
  - APA Policy Conference mailing list, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 7-8)
  - APA National Conference, Boston - media kit, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 9-11)
  - APA National Conference, Boston - student newspaper ads, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - APA National Conference, Boston - session speeches, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 13-16)
  - APA National Conference, Boston -program/background, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - APA National Conference, Boston - William H. Whyte, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Mayor Kevin White (includes photograph), Undated (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Arnold Brown (includes photograph), Undated (Box 2, Folder 20)
- William Reilly (includes photograph), Undated (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Keynote speeches, Undated (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Board of Directors meeting, Undated (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Boston's renewal release, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Board resolution release, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Rural Planning release, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Economic Development release, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Urban and Rural Conservation release, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Transportation release, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Housing release, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- New officers publicity, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Press advisory, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- New officers publicity, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Media registration, Undated (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Boston mailing list, Undated (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Publicity, Undated (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Land Use Law Seminar press releases, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- APA/NASA Commuter Aviation Conference coverage, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- APA/NASA Commuter Aviation Conference release, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 39)
- APA/NASA Commuter Aviation Conference, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 40, 43)
- Remote Sensing release, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 44)
- Dallas National Planning Conference
  - Dallas Planning Conference - public relations workshops, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Dallas Planning Conference - workshop comments, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Dallas National Planning Conference -media kit, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Dallas National Planning Conference -helicopter demonstration ride, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Dallas National Planning Conference -public/private partnerships, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Dallas National Planning Conference -Electric Utility Energy Workshop, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Dallas National Planning Conference -Garfield Schwartz on Urban Policy, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Dallas National Planning Conference -program/ logistics, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Dallas National Planning Conference -officers, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Dallas National Planning Conference-publicity, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Dallas National Planning Conference -Henry G. Cisneros Dallas National Planning Conference -Lester C. Thurow, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 4-5)
  - Dallas National Planning Conference -E.S. Savas, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Dallas National Planning Conference -William Norris, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Dallas National Planning Conference -Irving Hand, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Dallas National Planning Conference -media registration, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Dallas National Planning Conference -Steven Bollinger, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Dallas National Planning Conference -media advisory, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Dallas National Planning Conference -"APA News" public relations; "Leaders Letter" public relations, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Dallas National Planning Conference -talk show host letters, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Dallas National Planning Conference -public relations progress report, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Dallas National Planning Conference -Community and Outreach committee public relations progress report, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Dallas National Planning Conference- planning magazine publicity, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Dallas National Planning Conference Dallas, Texas planning issues, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Dallas National Planning Conference-mailing lists, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Special Responsibility Task Force, Undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
- "A Model of Growth Center Impact", 1982 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Newsroom fact sheets, Undated (Box 3, Folder 21-33)
- Women's Rights Committee, Undated (Box 3, Folder 34)
- Loft Conversions-coverage, Undated (Box 3, Folder 35)
- Loft conversions-media materials, Undated (Box 3, Folder 36-37)
- Water Resources Council release, Undated (Box 3, Folder 38)
- Water Conservation Report release, Undated (Box 3, Folder 39)
- Underground space, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 40)
- Radioactive waste, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 41)
- Presidents/new announcements (Irving Hand, Fred Bosselman), 1981 (Box 3, Folder 42)
- Planning Awards release, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 43-45)
- Mobile home regulations, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 46-48)
- Stephen Cochran Files
  - Stephen L. Cochran Files (Coordinator, Chapter/Division Services), November 1980 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Stephen L. Cochran Files, December 1980 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Stephen L. Cochran Files, January 1981 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Stephen L. Cochran Files, February 1981 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Stephen L. Cochran Files, March 1981 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Stephen L. Cochran Files, April 1981 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Stephen L. Cochran Files, May 1981 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Stephen L. Cochran Files, June 1981 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Stephen L. Cochran Files, July 1981 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Stephen L. Cochran Files, August 1981 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Stephen L. Cochran Files, September 1981 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Stephen L. Cochran Files, October 1981-December 1981 (Box 4, Folder 12-13)
  - Stephen L. Cochran Files, January-February 1982 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Stephen L. Cochran Files, March-April 1982 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Stephen L. Cochran Files, May-June 1982 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Stephen L. Cochran Files, July-August 1982 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Stephen L. Cochran Files, September-October 1982 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Stephen L. Cochran Files, November-December 1982 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Stephen L. Cochran Files, January-February 1983 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Stephen L. Cochran Files, March-April 1983 (Box 4, Folder 21-22)
  - Stephen L. Cochran Files, May 1983 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Stephen L. Cochran Files, June-July 1983 (Box 4, Folder 24-25)
  - Stephen L. Cochran Files, August-September 1983 (Box 4, Folder 26-27)
  - Stephen L. Cochran Files, October-November 1983 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Stephen L. Cochran Files, November 1983 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Stephen L. Cochran Files, January-February 1984 (Box 4, Folder 30-31)
  - Stephen L. Cochran Files, March 1984 (Box 4, Folder 32-33)
  - Stephen L. Cochran Files, April 1984 (Box 4, Folder 34, 36)
  - Stephen L. Cochran Files, May 1984 (Box 4, Folder 35, 37)
  - Stephen L. Cochran Files, June 1984 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Stephen L. Cochran Files, July 1984 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Stephen L. Cochran Files, August 1984 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Stephen L. Cochran Files, September 1984 (Box 4, Folder 41)
- Printed materials, Undated (Box 4, Folder 40-43)
- Printed materials, Undated (Box 5)
- APA National Applications Education Development Committee Recognition - Clemson University, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- University of Florida, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Howard University, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- University of Illinois at Urbana Champaign, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- University of Michigan, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- University of Nebraska - Lincoln, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 6-7)
- Ohio State University, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 8-9)
- University of Pennsylvania, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- San Jose State University, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- University of Texas at Arlington, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- California Polytechnic State University, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 13-17)
- University of California, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- University of Illinois at Chicago, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Southern National Illinois University, Edwardsville, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Iowa State University, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Iowa State University, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Morgan State University, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- University of North Carolina, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- North Dakota State University, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Ohio State University, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- University of Colorado, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- University of New Orleans, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- University of Tennessee, Knoxville, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 9-10)
- University of Wisconsin, Milwaukee, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 11-12)
- University of Hawaii at Monoa, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 13-15)
- Memphis State University, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- University of Miami, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Memphis State University, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Morgan State University, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 19-21)
- National Planning Award: Type I, Outstanding Planning Award, Undated (Box 7)
- St. Paul, Minnesota, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Coral Gables, Florida, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 2-3)
- Long Beach, California, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Washington, D.C. (application form only), 1985 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Cambridge, Massachusetts, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 6-7)
- Bantam Centre, Indonesia, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Applications, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Alabama - Auburn, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Arizona, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Arizona - Scottsdale, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- California - Big Sur, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- California - Big Sur River Protected Waterway Management Plan, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- California - Little Sur River Protected Waterway Management Plan, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- California - Big Sur Coast Land Use, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- California - Glendale, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- City of Glendale - Zoning Ordinance, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- California - Hayward, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- California - Merced County, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- California - Pleasanton, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- California - Rancho Cucamonga, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 14-15)
- California - San Francisco, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- California - China Town, San Francis???, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- California - Santa Monica Mountains, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- California - Tiburon, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Colorado - Boulder, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Colorado - Denver, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Delaware, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Florida - Pinellas County, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Florida - Tampa, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Georgia - Roswell, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Illinois - Arlington Heights, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- Illinois - Libertyville, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 27)
- Illinois - Schaumberg, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Louisiana - Jefferson Parish, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Maryland, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Maryland - Salisbury, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Michigan - Berkley, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Minnesota - Duluth, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- North Carolina - Winston-Salem, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Nevada - Clark County, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Nevada - Pine Forest, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- New York - Broome County, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 10-16)
- Oregon - Oregon City, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Oregon - Portland, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 18-25)
- Oregon - Salem, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 26)
- South Carolina - Lexington County, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Tennessee, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Texas - Corpus Christi (Chapman Ranch), 1987 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Vermont - Bennington County, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Virginia - Arlington, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Virginia - Arlington County, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 6-8)
- Virginia - Smith Mountain Lake, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Virginia - Virginia Beach, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Washington - Bellevue, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Washington - Gig Harbor, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Washington - Marysville, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Awards
  - Outstanding Specific Ordinance: Arizona - Pima County, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Distinguished Leadership: Planning Division - Glendale, California, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 15-18)
  - Distinguished Service: Davis, Lind, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Distinguished Service: Goldschmidt, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Distinguished Service: Harris, James L., 1987 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Distinguished Service: Lapp, Floyd, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Distinguished Leadership: Levine, Aaron, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Distinguished Service: Paternoster, Robert, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Distinguished Leadership - Rademan, Myles C., 1987 (Box 11, Folder 25-26)
  - Current Topic: Maryland - Baltimore, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Current Topic: New York - Orange County, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Current Topic: Washington, D.C., 1987 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Diana Donald Award: Thomas, Julia, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Paul Davidoff Award: Hall, Carlyle W., Jr., 1987 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Paul Davidoff Award: Maryland -Salisbury, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Karen B. Smith Chapter Achievement: Chapter, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Karen B. Smith Chapter Achievement: Virginia, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Division Achievement: Environmental Planning, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Division Achievement: Planning and Law Division, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 36)
- Chapter Newsletters
  - Newsletters 1974-1986Alabama Chapter Newsletters, January 1983-November 1985 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Alaska Chapter Newsletters, January 1981-October 1985 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Arkansas Chapter Newsletters, October 1984-March-June 1985 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - California Chapter Newsletters, October 1983-November 1985 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - California Chapter, San Diego Section Newsletters, October 1984-December 1985 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - "Capital Comments," National Capital Area Chapter, November 1984-December 1985 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Florida Chapter Newsletters, Winter 1982- November 1985 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - "Sun Coast Section," Florida Chapter Newsletters, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Georgia Chapter Newsletters, September 1984-September 1985 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Hawaii Chapter Newsletters, October 1983-December 1985 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Illinois Chapter Newsletter, April 1983-October 1985 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Indiana Chapter Newsletter, April 1977-Fall 1985 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Iowa Chapter Newsletters, Spring 1984-Summer 1985 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Kansas Chapter Newsletters, December 1983-December 1985 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Kentucky Chapter Newsletters, Fall 1980-November 1985 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Louisiana Chapter Newsletters, January 1984-Winter 1986 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Maryland Chapter Newsletters, October 1983-July 1985 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Michigan Chapter Newsletters, Fall 1983-Winter 1986 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Minnesota Chapter Newsletters, October 1983-December 1985 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Missouri Chapter Newsletters, Winter 1984-Autumn 1985 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Nebraska Chapter Newsletters, September 1979-November 1984 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Nevada Chapter Newsletters, December 1979-Winter 1986 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - "Bulletin Board," New England Chapter Newsletters, May 1984-December 1985 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - New Jersey Chapter Newsletters, April 1980-December 1985 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - New Mexico Chapter Newsletters, Spring 1980-Winter 1985 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - New York Metropolitan Chapter Newsletters, November 1984-November 1985 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - "Upstate Planning," New York Upstate Chapter Newsletters, February 1974-June 1984 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - North Carolina Newsletters, October 1984-November 1985 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Northern New England Chapter Newsletters, Fall 1980-Winter 1986 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Ohio Chapter Newsletters, December 1984-October 1985 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Oklahoma Chapter Newsletters, March 1976-March 1985 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Oregon Planners' Journal, (Chapter Newsletters), December 1983-October 1985 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - "Palmetto Planner" (South Carolina Chapter Newsletters), March 1984-June 1985 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Tennessee Chapter Newsletters, July 1978-July 1985 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Texas Chapter Newsletters, November 1984-December 1985 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - "Utah Planner" (Utah Chapter Newsletters., Nov. 1983-Nov. 1985 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Virginia Chapter Newsletters., Nov. 1983-Nov. 1985 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - "WAPA News," (Wisconsin Chapter Newsletters., Oct. 1983-Sept. 1985 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - "Washington Planning/Northwest. " (Washington State Chapter Newsletters)., Dec. 1983-Oct. 1985 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - West Virginia Chapter Newsletters., Dec. 1984-Fall/Winter 1985 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Neighborhood Development Newsletters., DateSummer 1980-Winter 1983 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Historic Preservation Newsletter., June 1982 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - State Planning Agency Newsletters., Aug. 1977-Oct. 1977 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - State Planning Division Newsletters., Mar. 1979-Dec. 1981 (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Arizona Chapter Newsletters., Feb. 1984-July 1985 (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - Planning Education Review Newsletter, Feb. 1975-Winter 1981 (Box 12, Folder 49)
- Accreditation Application - University of Montreal: Bachelors; Masters, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- University of North Carolina: Masters, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 2-4)
- University of Michigan: Masters, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Hunter College (C.U.N.Y.): Masters, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Michigan State University: Bachelor (BSUP); Masters (MUP), 1981 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- University of Iowa: Master of Art & Science in Urban and Regional Planning, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Alabama A & M: Master (MURP), 1975 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Alabama A & M: Master of Community Planning (MCP), 1981 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- University of Virginia: Bachelor of Planning, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- University of Virginia: Master of Planning, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- University of Rhode Island: Master Community Planning, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 13)